Large SAS-based companies
actually still have a lot of
intrinsic value due to the fact that they are
systems of records, so they have the data up
their sleeves, that's the
real value, they understand the processes of
those companies, they know how to sell
from other companies anyway, which is a
significant skill.  And in my opinion these
SAS will remain if they don't fall asleep at the
wheel.  If they don't
understand that AI is changing the world in the next 20 years, they
will probably be replaced.  But,
look, if you take big companies
compared to maybe even how they
behaved 20 years ago, they are much more
far-sighted.  The real disruption is
coming on the long tail of SAS, all
the small SAS banders, small to medium sized
businesses, everything is changing
extremely quickly.  Another thing that's
going to happen here, I'll give you a prediction,
maybe a little longer term.  For the
first time in our conversations,
we'll see an exponential growth of
new apps. We clearly play a
role in this explosion, but I don't think it
will continue in the long term because the
growth that will be even faster will be
that of interactions between
agents.  Apps are software in
general, user interfaces, they are almost
a legacy of the fact that
there were humans, there are humans
in front of your software, soon it will no
longer be necessary.  What will be done is you
will treat an agent as you treat your
employee, as you treat another
executive from another company.  G
you will ask I need this, these
are my requirements, this is my
budget.  I hope it will remain the
most social part of the web, and I don't mean
the brain rot of
constantly scrolling on social media, but
rather connecting people.
Discover new useful content,
discover tools, discover new agents.  It will be
a world where there will be hundreds,
thousands of agents per person.   We
will move from software as a service to
agent as a service.  There will be a future where we are
going.